Mushtaq Aslam

Islamabad, Islāmābād, Pakistan



mushtaq.aslam7@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mushtaq-aslam-05099511b

Summary

[EN]

I am a Full Stack Software Engineer currently working mainly in the Laravel MVC FrameWork, along PHP. I started my career as a PHP Backend Developer and then advanced to Laravel as a Backend framework. Along with PHP, I am confident with Html, JavaScript, and MySql and I have a pretty experience using Bootstrap as a frontend technology. Currently working on React as fronted developer and also has used Phython as programming language.

I have also experience with Version Control systems like "git" and working in teams for project development. I love finding new problems to solve or trying to build better solutions to a known problem. In my free time, I enjoy reading about new technologies and open-source projects.

If you want to get in touch, find me at 'mushtaq.aslam7@gmail.com'

Experience



📩 Full Stack Developer

medIQ Smart Healthcare
Mar 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)



Full-stack Developer

ZEEON

Dec 2021 - Mar 2022 (4 months)

Software Developer

Upwork, Fiverr, PeoplePerHour Mar 2020 - Mar 2022 (2 years 1 month)

Php/Laravel Developer Trainee

ZEEON

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021 (3 months)

Learned the different industry practices to develop different web applications.

Information Technology Support Officer

Sybrid Private Limited - A Lakson Group of Company

Jan 2021 - Aug 2021 (8 months)

installation and configuration of computer systems, diagnosing hardware and software faults and solved technical and application problems

Education



Riphah International University

Software Engineering, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services 2016 - 2020



Chand Bagh School

O' Levels, Engineering Sep 2006 - Apr 2011

Skills

Fiverr • Gigs • Amazon • Web Content Writing • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Web Application Development • jQuery • Programming Languages • WordPress • Git